collective2.com 2019-02-26

# Privacy Policy – Collective2

## Privacy Policy

This page was last updated on **May 24, 2018**.

**What This Privacy Policy Covers**

This policy covers how Collective2 treats personal information that Collective2 collects and receives. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, IP address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Collective2 does not own or control, or to people that Collective2 does not employ or manage.

**Information Collection and Use, General**

Collective2 collects personal information when you register with Collective2, and when you use Collective2 products or services. When you register we ask for information such as your name and email address. Once you register with Collective2 and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. Collective2 collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners, including information about trading advice you subscribe to. Collective2 automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, Collective2 cookie information, and the page you request. Collective2 uses this information to customize the content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

Collective2 does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you’ve requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

  * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Collective2 under confidentiality agreements. However, these companies do not have any independent right to use or share this information.
  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;
  * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Collective2’s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.
  * We transfer information about you if Collective2 is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Collective2 will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

###### **Cookies**

Collective2 may set and access Collective2 cookies on your computer. Advertisers or other companies do not have access toCollective2’s cookies.

**Your Ability to Edit Your Account Information**

You can edit your Collective2 Account Information, including your marketing preferences, at any time. Users can opt out of receiving future marketing communications or they can unsubscribe by following instructions contained in a message they receive. We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the Collective2 service, such as service announcements and administrative messages, that are considered part of your Collective2account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them.

**Confidentiality and Security**

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. Your Collective2 Account Information is password-protected. Collective2 uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions.

**Your Right To Be Forgotten**

If you really, really don’t like us, you can remove your account from our records entirely by   
going to https://collective2.com/removeaccount. If you use our automated trading service, we may archive certain trading-related information, even after removing you from our main application and marketing databases, in order to comply with rules imposed on us by U.S. and international financial regulators.

**Data Protection Officer**

We have appointed a Data Protection Officer. You can contact the person by emailing privacy@collective2.com.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Collective2 may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Collective2 account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.
